Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3
- Box: 54, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Item 20: Presidential address, 1974; Publication (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Item 21: General Secretary's Report: Sixth All-India Conference, Nripendra Nagar, Calcutta, 7th & 8th March 1981, Publication (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Item 22: Implement ILO Convention on hours of work (industry) and create job opportunities, 1981; Publication (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Item 23: General Secretary's Report to 24th Session of the All India Agricultural Workers' Union, 1982; Publication (Box 54, Folder 25)
    Author: Bharatiya Khet Mazdoor Union
- Box: 54, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Memorandum of settlement between the Tata Iron & Steel Co., Ltd., and the Tata Workers' Union, arrived at in conciliation proceedings held by the Conciliation Officer (Labour Commissioner), Bihar, 1959; Publication (Box 54, Folder 26)
    Author: Bihar (India). Labour Dept.
  - Item 2: Hind Mazdoor Sabha: Constitution, 1948; Publication (Box 54, Folder 26)
    Author: Hind Mazdoor Sabha
  - Item 3: Projects for plenty, 1951; Publication (Box 54, Folder 26)
    Author: India. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting
  - Item 4: Square deal for labour, 1951; Publication (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: More from mother earth, 1951; Publication (Box 54, Folder 26)
- Box: 54, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: A manual for foreign medical graduates, 1978; Publication (Box 54, Folder 27)
    Author: Physicians National Housestaff Association
- Box: 54, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1985; Publication (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1985; Publication (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Constitution, Publication (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: Constitution, Publication (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Item 5: Constitution, 1992; Publication (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Item 6: Constitution, 1985; Publication (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Item 7: Constitution, 1992; Publication (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Item 8: National Labour Institute: 1977-1982: a work report, Publication (Box 54, Folder 28)
    Author: National Labour Institute (India)
  - Item 9: National Labour Institute: 1977-1982: a work report, Publication (Box 54, Folder 28)
- Box: 54, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: An overview of socio economic condition of Indonesia on the first year of Pelita IV, 1984; Publication (Box 54, Folder 29)
    Author: Dep. Litbang
- Box: 54, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Equality for women workers, 1978; Publication (Box 54, Folder 30)
    Author: Irish Congress of Trade Unions
  - Item 2: Your union and you, Publication (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Structure and functions of Congress, Publication (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: Trades Councils model rules and notes for guidance, Publication (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: Executive Council Report, 1999/2001; Publication (Box 54, Folder 30)
    Author: Irish Congress of Trade Unions. Executive Council
    Notes: pt.II
  - Item 6: Executive Council Report, 1999/2001; Publication (Box 54, Folder 30)
    Notes: pt.I
  - Item 7: Report of proceedings ... biennial Delegate Conference, 1999; Publication (Box 54, Folder 30)
    Author: Irish Congress of Trade Unions. Delegate Conference
    Notes: 4th
- Box: 55, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Decreto-Ley Numero 121; El Jefe de Estado, en consejo de Ministros, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Decreto-Ley Numero 177; El Jefe de Estado, en Consejo de Ministros, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Tabla de Salario Minimo, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Decreto Numero 624; El Jefe de Estado, en consejo de Ministros, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Decreto Numero 943, La Junta Militar de Gobierno en Consejo de Ministros, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Decreto Numero 717; La Junta Militar de Gobierno, en Consejo de Ministros, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Decreto-Ley Numbero 177; El Jefe de Estado, en Consejo de Ministros, Publication (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Box: 55, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Gli aspetti della disoccupazione in provincia di Novara, 1953; Publication (Box 55, Folder 2)
    Author: Camera di commercio, industria e agricoltura di Novara
    Language: Italian.
- Box: 55, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: FISE information letter, 1987; Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
    Author: World Federation of Teachers' Unions
  - Item 2: La Voix du travailleur, 1982; Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
    Author: Union generale des travailleurs de Co^te d'Ivoire
    Notes: v.28
  - Item 3: La Voix du travailleur, 1982; Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30
  - Item 4: La Voix du travailleur, 1982; Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.31
  - Item 5: UGTCI: Special Congress, 1977; Publication (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Box: 55, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Affiliated Industrial Organizations, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    Author: Japanese Confederation of Labor
  - Item 2: Affiliated Industrial Organizations, Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Direct Line, 1975; Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    Author: International Federation of Journalists
  - Item 4: Domei Information, 1978; Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.78-01
  - Item 5: Domei Information, 1978; Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Domei Information, 1978; Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.78-02
  - Item 7: Domei Information, 1978; Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Domei Information, 1977; Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.77-01
  - Item 9: Domei Information, 1977; Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Domei Information, 1977; Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.77-02
  - Item 11: Domei Information, 1977; Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Journalist's World, 1963; Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    Notes: n.3
  - Item 13: Journalist's World, 1963; Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Journalist's World, 1963; Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Labour Relations Commissions in Japan, 1978; Publication (Box 55, Folder 4)
    Author: Central Labour Relations Commission
- Box: 55, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Revised Constitution of the Congress of Industrial Organizations Liberia, 1971; Publication (Box 55, Folder 5)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations, Liberia
- Box: 55, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Memorandum for - All Members thru the Stewards: Ratification of the Pema Constitution and its By=laws, as amended, 1971; Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
    Author: Philnabank Employees' Associaiton
  - Item 2: Memorandum for - All Members thru the Stewards: Ratification of the Pema Constitution and its By=laws, as amended, 1971; Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Collective Bargaining Agreement, Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
    Author: Philippine National Bank
  - Item 4: Collective Bargaining Agreement, Publication (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Box: 55, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Trade Union Congress of the Philippines, 1976; Publication (Box 55, Folder 7)
    Author: Trade Union Congress of the Philippines
  - Item 2: Constitution of the Trade Union Congress of the Philippines, 1976; Publication (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Box: 55, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Resolution of the Congress of the Coal Workers of Europe, 1932; Publication (Box 55, Folder 8)
    Author: Coal Workers of Europe
  - Item 2: Laws, etc., 1844; Publication (Box 55, Folder 8)
    Author: Great Britain
  - Item 3: Victoriae Reginae, 1867; Publication (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Ministry of Munitions of War, Publication (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Victoriae Reginae - Anno Decimo, 1847; Publication (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Box: 55, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Structure and function of the union, 1977; Publication (Box 55, Folder 9)
    Author: Amalgamated Union of Engineering Workers
  - Item 2: Structure and function of the union, 1972; Publication (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Structure and function of the union, 1972; Publication (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Structure and function of the union, 1972; Publication (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Box: 55, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: AES: Acuerdo Economico y Social, Publication (Box 55, Folder 10)
    Author: Union General de Trabajadores
- Box: 55, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Author: International Labor Office
    Notes: PR 41
  - Item 2: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 43
  - Item 3: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 44
  - Item 4: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 45
  - Item 5: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 46
  - Item 6: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 47
  - Item 7: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 48
  - Item 8: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 49
  - Item 9: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 50
  - Item 10: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 51
  - Item 11: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 52
  - Item 12: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 53
  - Item 13: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 58
  - Item 14: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 59
  - Item 15: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 60
  - Item 16: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 63
  - Item 17: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 64
  - Item 18: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 65
  - Item 19: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 68
  - Item 20: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 69
  - Item 21: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 71
  - Item 22: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 72
  - Item 23: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 73
  - Item 24: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 76
  - Item 25: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 77
  - Item 26: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 78
  - Item 27: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 82
  - Item 28: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 85
  - Item 29: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 86
  - Item 30: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 87
  - Item 31: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 88
  - Item 32: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 89
  - Item 33: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 90
  - Item 34: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 92
  - Item 35: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 94
  - Item 36: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 95
  - Item 37: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 96
  - Item 38: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 97
  - Item 39: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 3
  - Item 40: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 4
  - Item 41: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 5
  - Item 42: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 6
  - Item 43: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 9
  - Item 44: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Item 45: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 10
  - Item 46: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 17
  - Item 47: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 18
  - Item 48: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 32
  - Item 49: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 36
  - Item 50: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 37
  - Item 51: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 38
  - Item 52: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 39
  - Item 53: Press News from the International Labor Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 11)
    Notes: PR 40
- Box: 55, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Minutes of meeting of the International Bureau held at the Head Office, Publication (Box 55, Folder 12)
    Author: International Gament Worekers' Federation
  - Item 2: To: All Affiliated to Organisations, 1960; Publication (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: To: All Affiliated to Organisations, 1958; Publication (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: To: All Affiliated to Organisations, 1959; Publication (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: The anaylsis of essential features of the textile industry in certain countries, 1968; Publication (Box 55, Folder 12)
    Author: International Textile and Garment Workers' Federation
  - Item 6: Report of Activities, 1965; Publication (Box 55, Folder 12)
    Author: Leong Fook Kee
  - Item 7: Report of Activities, 1965; Publication (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Information concerning the Knitting Industry in Hong Kong, 1965; Publication (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: A charter for Garment Workers, Publication (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: Report of the Special Conference on Problems of the Common Market, 1962; Publication (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Box: 55, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: COPSITU: Conference of Public Service Independent Trade Unions: An introduction, Publication (Box 55, Folder 13)
    Author: Conference of Public Service Trade Unions
  - Item 2: COPSITU: Conference of Public Service Independent Trade Unions: An introduction, Publication (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: COPSITU: Conference of Public Service Independent Trade Unions: An introduction, Publication (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: COPSITU: Conference of Public Service Independent Trade Unions: An introduction, Publication (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Box: 55, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: A guide to Employers Obligations, Publication (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: The disabled persons register, Publication (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Ministry of Labour Gazette, 1961; Publication (Box 55, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.49:no.6
  - Item 4: Organisation and Functions of the Ministry of Labour, 1961; Publication (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: The Organisation of the Employment Exchange Service in Great Britain, 1960; Publication (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Box: 55, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Public Service: The voice of NALGO, 1978; Publication (Box 55, Folder 15)
    Author: National and Local Government Officers Association
    Notes: v.52:n.4
  - Item 2: Facts about NALGO, Publication (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Box: 55, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: N.U.M. Membership 1951-1977 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: N.U.M. Membership 1951-1977 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: The History of the National Union of Mineworkers, Publication (Box 55, Folder 16)
    Author: National Union of Mine Workers
  - Item 4: The History of the National Union of Mineworkers, Publication (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Miner: Special Ballot Issue, Publication (Box 55, Folder 16)
    Author: National Executive Committee
  - Item 6: Miner: Special Ballot Issue, Publication (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Miner: Special Ballot Issue, Publication (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Miner, 1979; Publication (Box 55, Folder 16)
    Notes: Oct/Nov
  - Item 9: Miner, 1979; Publication (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Box: 55, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Memorandum of Agreement, 1919; Publication (Box 55, Folder 17)
    Author: National Amalgamated Union of Enginement, Firemen, Mechanics, Motormen & Electrical Workers
  - Item 2: Memorandum of Agreement, Publication (Box 55, Folder 17)
    Author: Worsted and Woollen Industries
  - Item 3: Agreement for Trials of Proposals on Manpower Utilisation and Payment Structure between Imperial Chemical Industries Limited and the Trades Unions Concerned, Publication (Box 55, Folder 17)
    Author: Imperial Chemical Industries Limited
- Box: 55, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Trades Union Congress, Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
    Author: Trades Union Congress
  - Item 2: Pay, Productivity and Income Distribution: Memorandum by the TUC, 1988; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: News from the TUC, 1993; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Campaign for jobs and recovery: 1993 Budget, Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Industrial News for the use of the Press, 1972; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.1
  - Item 6: Industrial News for the use of the Press, 1972; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.3
  - Item 7: Industrial News for the use of the Press, 1972; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.4
  - Item 8: Industrial News for the use of the Press, 1972; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.5
  - Item 9: Industrial News for the use of the Press, 1972; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.7
  - Item 10: Industrial News for the use of the Press, 1972; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.8
  - Item 11: Industrial News for the use of the Press, 1972; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.9
  - Item 12: Industrial News for the use of the Press, 1972; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.10
  - Item 13: Industrial News for the use of the Press, 1972; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.11
  - Item 14: TUC handbook on the MSC's Youth Training Scheme, 1983; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 15: TUC Women's Conference Report 1988, Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 16: Action education: a TUC guide for trade unionists, 1983; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 17: The Unequal health of the nation, 1982; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 18: Programme for recovery, 1982; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 19: The battle for jobs, 1983; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 20: Trades Unions and black workers, 1986; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 21: Trade unions in the cities, 1988; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 22: Women in the labour market: a TUC report, 1983; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Item 23: Working women: TUC discussion book for all trade unionists, 1983; Publication (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Box: 55, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Soviet Trade Unions: Journal of the All-Union Central council of Trade Unions, 1982; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Soviet Trade Unions: Journal of the All-Union Central council of Trade Unions, 1982; Publication (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Box: 56, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Notes complementaires sur las structure economique et financiere, 1959; Publication (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: International Joint Commission of the Shipbuilding and Ship ?Repair Industries of the Metalworkers TUI, 1960; Publication (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Box: 56, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Le fonti di energia e il piano del lavoro, 1950; Publication (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Author: Giuseppe Regis
- Box: 56, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 50 anni di lotte operaie in Apuania: 1901-1951, 1952; Publication (Box 56, Folder 3)
    Author: Antonio Bernieri
- Box: 56, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Propettiva Sindacale, 1976; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Le relazioni umane e sociali nell'azienda, 1954; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Author: Confederazione italiana sindacati lavoratori
  - Item 3: Una economia forte per un sindacato forte, 1953; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Una giusta rivendicazione salariale, 1953; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: I lavoratori difendono l"Italia, 1951; Publication (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Box: 56, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Solidarieta per il lavoro, Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Lavoro e solidarieta` in Italia e in Europa, 1989; Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
    Author: Confederazione italiana sindacati lavoratori. Congresso confederale
  - Item 3: Indagine conoscitiva sullo stato organizzativo delle strutture, 1979; Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
    Author: Unione Italiana del Lavoro
  - Item 4: Capire il nuovo guidare il cambiamento, 1981; Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
    Author: Pierre Carniti
  - Item 5: Capire il nuovo guidare il cambiamento, 1981; Publication (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Box: 56, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Statuts et reglement interieur, 1981; Publication (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Box: 56, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Rapport moral et d'activites presente par, 1977; Publication (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Theme: Quatorze annees de syndicalisme bilan et perspectives, 1975; Publication (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Guide de l'assure socials, 1981; Publication (Box 56, Folder 7)
    Author: Caisse nationale de prevoyance sociale (Co^te d'Ivoire)
- Box: 56, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Constitution, rules and regulations of the National Workers Union of Jamaica, Publication (Box 56, Folder 8)
    Author: National Workers Union (Jamaica)